--==本影片由 CMCT 團隊 榮譽出品==--
更多精彩影視 請訪問 http://cmct.cc
影片壓制:陽陽  字幕來源:射手網  調校:zzpals  招募Q號:76846146
警察學校
你好
Hello...
泰格貝利
Tackleberry.
我們會想念你的
We're all gonna miss you around here.
警察學院培育了你這樣一位憂秀的警察
The Police Academy's getting itself a real fine recruit.
呢 我可以
May I, uh...
走了嗎?
go now?
是的 先生
Affirmative, sir.
明白
Ten-four.
請自便
Yes, of course. Ten-four.
原來是你們
You guys.
想給你個驚喜
Surprise.
停車場都滿了 先生
Lot's full, mister.
別跟我廢話
Look, don't give me that crap.
- 你一定得找個空位 - 全都滿了
- You've got a space. - The lot's full, sir, really.
給我找個空位 白癡
Find a spot, dickhead.
- 白癡 - 是的 你們經理呢?
- Dickhead? - That's right. Where's the manager?
你剛才說"白癡"?
Dickhead?
給我泊車 臭屁
Park the car, butt breath.
- 你說"臭屁"? - 是的
- Butt breath? - Yeah.
等等 別忙 你戴著假髮 是嗎?
Wait a minute. Hold everything. That's a wig, isn't it?
- 停好車 - 真是假髮啊
- Ahem. Park the car. - Yeah, that's a wig.
假髮 假髮
Wig! Wig! Dong-dong-dong!
- 警惕假髮 警惕假髮 - 我叫你泊車混蛋 閉嘴
- Wig alert! Wig alert! Dong-dong-dong! - Park the car, asshole. Shut up.
姑娘們 快來看啊這是假髮
Girls. It's a rug.
究竟發生了什麼事? 嗨 魯
What the hell's going on here? Hi, Lou.
- 魯 - 這無禮的小流氓不絕我泊車
- Lou? - This rude little punk won't park my car.
馬洪尼 替這位先生泊車
Mahoney, park this car.
車健全都滿了
If you can find a spot--
馬上去 否則炒你魷魚 明白嗎? 炒魷魚
Do it now or you're fired. You understand? Fired.
這不公平 這傢伙態度極差
Fired? That's not fair, the guy has a bad attitude.
快去
Do it, okay?
我要你先給這位先生道歉再替他停車
I want you to apologize to this man, then park his car.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
- 對不起 - 滾吧
- I'm sorry. - Get out of here.
把煙灰缸也清理掉
And clean the ashtray while you're at it.
真對不起 魯 現在就是找不到好幫手
Yeah, I'm sorry, Lou. You just can't get good help these days.
他們不尊重官人也不愛護財物
Respect for anything. They don't respect customers.
他們甚至不懂得尊重是什麼
They don't respect property. They don't respect respect.
要命 老天
Holy shit. Jesus.
剛剛好 合適得不得了
It fits. Damn thing fits.
我以為沒有空位子原來還有一個
I thought there were no more spaces. Am I an idiot or what?
嗨 夥計們
Hi, fellas.
嘿 夥計們 只是
Hey, guys, just--
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey!
我想我不該弄濕這些照片的
Guys, I don't think I'm supposed to get the photos wet.
你們會為此付出代價的我說到做到
You're going to pay for this. Mark my words.
想知道為什麼嗎?
And you want to know why? Huh?
告訴你們好了 這不是什麼秘密 人人都知道
I'll let you know why. It's no secret. Everybody knows.
我要加入警隊
I'm joining the police force. Ha, ha!
你們怕了吧?
What do you think of that, huh? Huh?
到時看是誰怕誰
Now who's in charge?
警官 又是他
Hey, sarge, it's him again.
我會通知裏德上尉 坐到那邊去 馬洪尼
I'll call Captain Reed. Sit over there, Mahoney.
好吧 我們走吧
All right, let's go.
坐下 別亂動
Sit. And stay there.
- 你是怎麼進來的? - 讓你見識見識
- What are you in for? - I'll show you.
天殺的 快停下
Goddamn it! Stop that!
啊 長官 不是說您
Oh, no, sir. No, not you.
棒極了 真的
That's terrific. Really.
- 你的大名? - 喬斯 拉維爾．喬斯
- What's your name? - Jones. Larvell Jones.
拉維爾．喬斯
Monsignor Larvell Jones.
喬斯
M.D.
- 我們走吧 馬洪尼 - 再見 拉維爾
- Let's go, Mahoney. - See you around, monsignor.
是拉維爾博士
Doctor monsignor.
為什麼你就不能少惹點麻煩?
Why can't you stay out of trouble?
我的意思是
I mean...
你到底是怎麼回事? 上星期 擾亂治安；
What's wrong with you? Last week: disturbing the peace.
上上個星期又破壞私有財產
Week before that: destroying private property.
要經常為你開罪 我真是煩透了
And I'm getting tired of saving your butt.
我救你只是為了你父親
I only do it because of your father.
- 他曾是我的好朋友 - 我知道
- He was a good friend. - Yeah, I know.
馬洪尼 我已經決定了
Now, Mahoney, I've made a decision.
這次 我不會幫你了
I ain't gonna help you this time.
我得請你去監獄裏坐坐
You're going to the county lockup.
- 監獄? - 對
- Lockup? - Mm-hm.
為什麼? 我做的事情也沒什麼大不了的
Why? I didn't do anything really major.
- 那我們來個協定 怎樣? - 什麼都行
- Then I'll make a deal with you. - Anything.
我要你去警察學院
I want you to go to the Police Academy.
警察學院?
The Police Academy?
就算你畢不了業 訓練對你也有好處
Even if you never graduate, the training will be good for you.
等等
Wait a minute.
你說什麼 裏德?
Wait a minute. Reed?
聽著 你沒看電視廣告嗎?
Listen, you've seen the commercials on TV.
警察學校正在招兵買馬
The Academy's taking all kinds these days.
誰都能進去
Anybody can get in.
你也能
Even you.
免談 簡直是瘋了
No deal. That's nuts.
要麼進警察學院 要麼進監獄
Well, it's either that or the lockup.
- 警察學院和監獄 二選一 - 我會有自己的警車嗎?
- Police Academy or jail. - Will I get my own squad car?
你將接受14個星期的訓練
You'll get 14 weeks of Academy training and discipline...
- 就從星期一早上開始 - 14個星期
- starting Monday morning. - Fourteen weeks.
學校可以開除你
Oh, they can throw you out.
但是你不能退出不然就回來坐牢
But you can't quit. You quit, and you're back in jail.
這就是我們之間的協定
That's the deal.
- 我可以叫上個朋友一起去嗎? - 誰?
- Can I bring a friend? - Who?
他叫拉維爾．喬斯 是我的私人醫生
Monsignor Larvell Jones, my personal physician.
這個由你決定好了
You decide.
親愛的 別走 我愛你 我不想你受傷
Honey, please don't go. I love you. I don't want to see you hurt.
我好擔心啊 你總是容易出什麼意外
I worry about you. You're so accident-prone.
警察學校是個危險的地方
And the Police Academy is such a dangerous place.
- 親愛的 別擔心 我會沒事的 - 嗯
- Honey, don't worry. I'll be okay. - Unh!
一切都會順利的
Everything'll be okay.
你敢起動車子 你就死定了
You start that car and you're a dead man, buster.
親愛的 我要遲到了
Honey, I'm late.
你敢開出馬路 我就殺了你
You pull out of that driveway and I'll have your head on a pole.
給我回來 你這個笨蛋
Come back here, you turkey!
再往前一步 就死定了 混蛋 聽到沒有?
You move this car an inch and you're finished, mister. You hear me?
為什麼偏偏要做警察?
Of all the things that you could be in this world, why a policeman?
是做女警 媽媽
A policewoman, mother.
可為什麼?
But Why?
因為刺激
Because it's exciting, it's different.
做女警有機會遇上有趣的人
It'll give me a chance to meet interesting and unusual people.
現在 如果你不靠邊停車
right now! If you don't pull over--
不像你和我
People who aren't like you and me.
- 快看啊 是警長 - 真的嗎?
- Hey, look, it's the chief. - Really?
嘿 提提我的名字
Hey, mention my name.
軍校生凱爾·布朗克斯報到
Cadet Kyle Blankes reporting for duty, sir.
滾開 混蛋
Get away from me, you asshole.
是 長官
Yes, sir.
- 這是哪兒 老兄? - 厄瓜多爾
- Where are we, man? - Ecuadon
我到了 我得走了 再見
Okay! Oh, here we are. I got to go now. Bye.
- 再見 甜豌豆 再見 可愛的餡餅 - 我們會想念你的
- Bye, sweet-pea. Bye, cutie-pie. - We'll miss you.
- 好吧 - 再見
- Okay. - Bye!
好的 姑娘們 記住我愛你們
Okay, girls. Remember, I love yous.
四處介紹一下你自己吧
- Bye! - Introduce yourself around, man.
再見 再見 親愛的 再見
Bye! Bye, babies. Goodbye.
嗨 打擾了
Hey, excuse me.
- 那些姑娘 你全認識嗎? - 當然
- Do you know all those women? - Sure.
- 她們是我的女友 - 全部都是嗎?
- They're my girlfriends. - All of them?
- 是的 - 卡裏·馬洪尼
- Yeah. - Carey Mahoney.
我是喬治·馬丁
I'm George Martin, Carey.
我們做朋友吧 你真有趣
We should be pals. You're an interesting guy.
你是新生嗎?
You a cadet?
開除前是
I am until I can get myself thrown out of here.
10點之前 我會離開
I'll be gone by 10:00.
進警校就為被開除?
You, like, joined the Academy to get thrown out?
對
That's right.
你不也挺有趣?
Hey, you're a pretty interesting guy yourself.
你瞧
Look at that.
快瞧一瞧
Just look at that.
看看那些人渣 在我那個年代．
Look at that scum. When I went through this academy...
每個學生都有標準身高 體重 膚色
every cadet was the right weight, the right height, color...
他們都有 約翰遜 羅薩德
and they all had Johnsons, Lassard.
人人都是
Every single one of them.
什麼玩意兒?
Johnsons?
就是這個
You know...
哦 是的
Oh, yes.
那時 放眼望去 全都是男生啊
Back in the old days, there were Johnsons as far as the eye could see.
真讓人懷念啊
And what a lovely sight it was.
你看過這些申請表了嗎?
Have you seen these applications?
你可知 新任女市長給我們帶來什麼?
Have you seen what our new lady mayor has brought us?
你可知 她正在毀滅
Do you know she is attempting to dismantle...
我們這所全美國最有紀律的學校?
one of this country's great institutions of law and order?
你怎麼看?
What do you say to that, Lassard?
這個婊子
The bitch.
- 指揮官? - 是的 局長
- Commandant? - Yes, chief.
市長要我們接受這些廢物
The mayor says we've got to take this flotsam.
但我們不一定要讓他們都成為警察
But that doesn't mean we have to put them on the force.
你明白我的意思嗎?
You get my drift?
把礙眼的雜草除掉
Weed the undesirables out.
- 除掉他們 - 沒問題 部長
- Get rid of them. - No problem, chief.
今天早上就開始除草
We'll start washing them out this morning.
不是我們開除他們
We don't throw them out.
而是要叫他們自動乖乖離開
They must be encouraged to quit on their own.
- 明白嗎? - 我明白了 部長
- Do you understand? - I think I understand, sir.
謝謝 哈里少尉 我知道你會明白的
Thank you, Lieutenant Harris, I'm sure you do.
- 羅薩德? - 什麼?
- Lassard? - What?
你明白嗎?
Do you understand?
- 再明白不過了 部長 - 很好
- It's clear as glass, chief. - Good.
那麼我們全都知道該怎麼做了
Then we all know what to do.
就是這樣
That's it...
我去 這麼多黑鬼
There sure are a lot of spades around here.
這樣也沒什麼不好
Which I think is good.
這對警校有好處
Very good for the Academy.
你究竟來這裏幹什麼?
What the hell are you doing here?
我… 想當一名警官
I want to be a police officer.
什麼? 我聽不到
What? I can't hear you.
我… 我… 想當警官
I want to be a police officer.
- 做夢 - 是的
- Don't unpack. - Well...
我該被開除了
time to get thrown out.
公主 快回來
Princess. Princess! Prin-- !
- 你叫什麼名字 新兵? - 湯普森 長官
- What's your name, Cadet? - Thompson, sir.
- 你住在這附近嗎? - 不 長官
- You live around here? - No, sir.
你的電話號碼呢?
What's your telephone number, Thompson?
快說啊 向前看 電話號碼?
Come on, eyes front. Telephone number.
5552467 先生
5-5-5 2-4-6-7, sir.
好吧 讓我瞧瞧你的大腿
Okay, let's see the thighs.
快 我這一整天都沒看到了 大腿
Come on, come on. I haven't got all day. The thighs.
- 你在搗什麼蛋? - 泡姐 長官
- What in the hell are you doing? - Meeting women, sir.
你叫什麼名字 混蛋?
What's your name, dirtbag?
- 混蛋? - 你的名字?
- Dirtbag? - Your name?
馬洪尼 先生
Mahoney, sir.
歸列 馬洪尼
Back in line, Mahoney.
長官 可否商量一下?
Sir, can I have a second with you? Um, listen. Uh...
我並不居於這裏 也不適合這裏
I don't really belong here. I'm not right for this.
回去站好
Get back in line.
馬上
Now!
媽咪 別急 快回來 公主
Mom, it's all right. Don't worry. Come here, Princess.
我是拉薩校長 歡迎加入警隊
My name is Commandant Lassard. Welcome to the new police force.
你們的訓練是
Your training time here will last...
十四
Fourteen.
14個星期
fourteen weeks.
你們將要學習使用武器、辦案程序、地方法律—
You will be schooled in firearms, police procedures, local laws...
以及許多其他的知識
and many, many other things.
12個星期之後 你們中間某些人 將會成為警官
After those 12 weeks, some of you will be police officers...
某些則會被淘汰
and some of you will not.
有些人會
Some of you will be--
在這所學校
Here at the Academy...
在這所學校裏．
你們將會學到
you will learn...
You will learn...
公主 公主 來到這裏
Princess. Princess. Come here.
公主? 它更像王子
Princess? Looks more like a prince to me.
- 把狗給我 - 但這是我的狗 長官
- Give me that dog. - Uh-- Ahem. But he's mine, sir.
但它是個怪物
He's a queer.
到庫房去領取你們的制服
Cadets, proceed to the supply room and draw your uniforms.
解散 走吧 動起來 動起來
Fall out. Let's go. Move it. Move it, move it, move it.
- 下一個 - 槍呢? 幾時發槍?
- Next. - What about guns? When do we get guns?
下一個
Next.
- 我穿9碼 10碼也行 - 下一個
- I'm a size 9, sometimes a size 10. - Next.
嘿 你們三個混蛋 先給我去理髮
Hey! You three dirtbags report to the Academy barber...
在你們做任何事情之前
before you do anything else.
可是在哪兒?
Where's that?
找吧 呆子
Find it, rat face.
"呆子"?
Rat face?
- 他是說另外那個人 - 哦 明白
- He probably meant the other guy. - Oh. Oh, okay.
- 那是什麼? - 校長和他的妻子
- What's that? - That's where the commandant...
- 就住在那棟房子裏 - 真好
- and his wife live. - Nice.
對不起 請問在哪裏領制服?
Oh. Excuse me. Do you know where we get our clothes?
在你的右邊 就在那兒
Yeah. You gotta go right over there.
- 在這裏? 好的 謝謝 - 嗯
- Here? Okay, thanks. - Mm-hm.
- 走進去後 告訴他們是馬洪尼讓你去的 - 明白
- Go in and tell them Mahoney sent you. - Got it.
- 3點前要離開這裏 - 滾開 混蛋 我先理
- Be out of here by 3:00. - Move it, dirtbag. I'm first.
我排第二
And I'm next.
好吧 你們先理
For important guys like you, I'll wait.
我要剃光頭
Okay, let's go. Take it all off.
你猜對了
You got it.
嗨?
Hello?
- 兩邊修一修就可以了 - 當然
- Ah. Just a little off the side, please. - You bet.
- 那樣可以嗎? - 當然可以 這兒又不是軍隊
- You can do that? - Sure. This ain't the Army, you know.
跟我來 為你們這些小寶貝 找個睡覺的地方
Let's go, let's go! We've got to find you little babies a place to sleep.
給我聽清楚了 豬頭
Better listen up, you fart-blossoms.
- 你確定你說對了我的名字? - 當然 我還拼了出來的
- You sure you said Mahoney? - Yeah, I even spelled it to her.
- 科普蘭牙和布郎克斯在這一間 - 長官
- Copeland and Blankes, in here. - Sir.
他是我的私人醫生 我不能沒有他
This man is my personal physician. I can't live without him, sir.
費克勒牙和馬丁住這間
Right down here, I want Fackler and Martin.
從小我就認識他了
I've known him since childhood--
- 馬洪尼牙和泰格貝利住這間 - 是 長官 謝謝 長官
- Right here, Mahoney and Tackleberry. - Yes, sir! Thank you, sir!
我一直希望能和一個瘋子住在一起
Thank you. I've always wanted to live with a nut.
榮幸之至
My pleasure.
- 你叫馬洪尼 是嗎? - 是的 長官 我想再說一句
- Mahoney, is it? - Yes, sir. I'd like to say one more--
其餘的廢物跟我來 快 快 快
The rest of you wimps come with me. Move it, move it, move it.
廢物
Wimps?
- 你結婚了? - 是的
- You're married, huh? - Yeah.
真棒
That's beautiful, man.
對我來說 婚姻是神聖的
To me, marriage is a sacred institution.
你告訴我
So tell me.
你和妻子做愛的時候 是用狗仔式 還是別的?
You and the wife do it doggie-style or what?
房子已收拾好 正等待檢查 長官
Room ready for inspection, sir.
頭理得好 孩子
Good haircuts, men.
- 謝謝你 先生 - 謝謝 先生
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
這該死的好髮型
Damn good haircuts.
- 謝謝你 先生 - 謝謝 先生
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
孩子
Men...
我現在有個小麻煩
I've got a little problem.
我似乎帶了一群笨蛋學生
It seems I've got a squad full of scumbuckets.
淨是些沒用的垃圾
A whole big bunch of losers.
我希望你們兩位憂秀的新生
And I was kind of hoping that you two fine, young cadets...
可以幫我清理一些垃圾
might help me to just get rid of a few of them.
怎麼樣? 你能幫我嗎?
What do you say? Will you help me out?
- 當然 先生 - 非常好
- Yes, sir. - Good.
- 好的 - 我是查德·科普蘭 長官
- Good. - I'm Copeland, sir. Chad Copeland.
好名字
Good for you.
我叫道格拉斯·費克勒 我一直都想當警察
Hi, I'm Douglas Fackler. I always wanted to be a cop.
霍夫曼中尉 霍夫曼中尉…
- Lieutenant Hoffman, Lieutenant Hoffman...
立即到醫務室報到
report immediately to the infirmary.
嘿 湯普森
Hey, Thompson. Well?
- 我穿制服好看嗎? - 今天早上並不好玩
- How do I look? - That wasn't very funny this morning.
我並不想捉弄你 我真的想看看你的美腿
Wasn't funny. I'd give anything to see your thighs.
告訴我吧
Don't suppose you'd describe them for me.
古銅色 非常柔軟 豐滿
Well, they're tan, of course. Very supple, well-rounded...
手感也很好
and luxuriant to the touch.
嗯
Mm.
絕對安靜
Absolute silence!
我是哈利少尉．
My name is Lt. Harris...
別忘了
in case you missed it.
這位是卡拉漢警官
This is Sgt. Callahan...
也別忘了
in case you missed it.
我們是這所學校裏 最嚴格的教官
We are the meanest instructors here.
我們要訓練你們 因為你們 是這裏最糟糕的學生
We've got you because you are the worst people here.
你們是D班
You people are D-Squad.
D代表混蛋的意思
D for dirtbags.
當我說"嘿 混蛋" 那就是在叫你們
When I say, "Hey, dirtbags," that means you.
你們將會痛恨我一輩子
You people are going to hate my guts for the rest of your lives.
我會讓你們 為進入這間警校而感到後悔
I am going to make you sorry that you ever came here.
按照學校慣例
Now, it is traditional here at the Academy for each squad...
每個班 有兩個學生班長
to have two student squad-leaders.
布朗克牙和科普蘭為班長 出列
I have chosen Cadets Blankes and Dopeland. Step out, men.
當兩位班長下命令時
If these two cadets give you an order...
你們要好好遵守
obey it.
現在 我認為這將是一個好的開始
Now, I thought it would be nice...
第一天下午的集訓 就以繞著學校散步來結束
if we were to close out our first afternoon together...
我想這是件快樂的事
with a nice little stroll around the campus.
快跑 你們這些屎蟲
Move out, maggots!
- 哦 見鬼 - 這肯定不是什麼厄瓜多爾
- Holy, shit. - This is definitely not Ecuador.
起來 芭芭拉 快跑
Get up, Barbara. Get up. Get up.
快跑 快跑
Move it, move it, move it.
小心屁股開花 死胖子
I could show a movie on your butt, fatso.
十九 二十
Nineteen. Twenty!
更多 我要更多
More! I want more!
十五
Fifteen.
十六
Sixteen.
十七
Seventeen.
十八 再來 再來
Eighteen. Let's go. Let's go.
九 十
Nine. Ten.
請注意 十分鐘後熄燈
Attention. Lights out in 10 minutes.
Lights out in 10 minutes.
結束
Game over.
混蛋
Asshole.
你們將會
Police work...
在這裏
is what...
學習
you are...
如何當警察
here for.
拘捕
Arrest...
程序
procedures...
管理交通
traffic violations...
高速
high-speed...
駕駛
driving...
自我保護
self-defense.
同時還有許多考… 試
And you will have many examinations...
必須通過
which you must pass.
另外
Plus...
你們還得進行殘酷的體能特訓
you will endure an extremely rigorous physical training program.
知道這意味著什麼嗎 胡克絲?
Do you know what that means, Hooks?
我不知道 長官
I'm not sure, sir.
你說什麼?
What?
聲音大一點
Voice commands.
你們說話要有威嚴
We will learn to use our voices with authority.
不會嗎?
Won't we, Hooks?
你們可有人受過軍事訓練?
Now, have any of you had any military training?
嗯
Mm-hm?
我曾在空軍第209特種部隊服役
I served with the U.S. Army Airborne 209th Special Forces Unit.
還有誰?
Anybody else?
什麼
What?
你也接受過軍訓?
You have had prior military training, Mahoney?
- 是的 不過是上輩子的事 - 你說什麼
- Well, yes, but not in this life, sir. - What?
上輩子 我曾在印度女王的部隊服役
In a previous life, I served with Her Majesty's Forces in India.
- 有趣的副業 - 如果你想讓我們開除你
- Interesting sideline - If you're trying to get thrown out...
絕對沒門 馬洪尼
I'm afraid that's quite impossible.
"沒門"? 怎麼回事?
Impossible? What the hell's going on here?
我要去見校長
I'll have to see the commandant about this.
您還將學習市政法規 你們要用心學習它們
You will also learn the Municipal Code. And you will learn them by heart.
學員 馬洪尼
Cadet Mahoney. Cadet Mahoney.
請立刻到拉薩校長辦公室來
Report immediately to the commandant's office. Cadet Mahoney.
好吧 馬洪尼 快去 用跑的
Okay, Mahoney, get going. On the double. Move it. Move it. Move it.
現在
Now--
哈里少尉
Lieutenant Harris, Lieutenant Harris...
請立刻到射擊場來
report immediately to the firing range. Lieutenant Harris.
對不起
Excuse me.
卡拉漢 交給你了
Callahan, take over.
你好
Howdy.
誰讓你進來的?
- No one's allowed in here. - Listen.
- 打擾您了 警長 - 我是校長 不是"警長"
- I got a problem, chief. - It's commandant.
對不起 校長 是你養的魚嗎?
Commandant, I'm sorry. Is that your fish?
- 不 是朋友的 - 真漂亮
- No, it belongs to a friend. - Very pretty.
- 你有什麼事? - 我要離開這裏
- What do you want? - I want out of here. Right now.
- 離開這辦公室? - 不 是離開這學校
- Out of this office? - No, out of the Academy.
- 沒問題 你可以退出 - 我不能退出
- That's no problem. You can just quit. - I can't quit.
為什麼不能? 許多憂秀的人都退出了
Of course you can. Many, many wonderful people...
- 已經退出了很多很多 - 校長?
- have quit many, many - Commandant?
你認識裏德上尉嗎?
Do you know Capt. Reed?
哦 是的 裏德上尉 你就是馬洪尼
Oh, yes. Capt. Reed. You're Mahoney.
馬洪尼
Mahoney. Mahoney. Mahoney.
- 你的情況特殊 你不能退出 - 我知道
- You're a special case. You can't quit. - I know that.
- 我也不能開除你 - 為什麼不能?
- On the other hand, I can't throw you out. - Why not?
因為我答應了裏德上尉 要把你留在這裏24個星期
I promised Capt. Reed. I promised I'd keep you here the full 24 weeks.
你說什麼?
You what? You what? You told-- ?
不 他說我可以
He told me that I could...
- 我被困在這裏了? - 是 誰不是呢?
- I'm trapped here? - Well, yes. We all are.
繼續前進 向那座山前進
Pick it up, pick it up. Keep moving up that hill.
加油
Put some muscle in it.
膝蓋抬高 膝蓋抬高 加油
Get those knees up. Get those knees up, come on!
快點 快點 快點
Hustle, hustle, hustle!
這絕對不適合我
This is definitely not for me.
繼續
Keep going!
快點 胡克絲 爬過去 快 快
Come on, Hooks, get over the wall. Move it, move it, move it.
快點 胡克絲 起來
Come on, Hooks, get up.
算了吧 繞過去 你爬不過去的 為什麼還不退出?
Skip it. Go around. You'll never make it. Why don't you quit now?
滾 滾 你永遠也爬不過去的
Quit, quit, quit. You'll never make it.
對不起 長官 我扯破了褲子
Sir, I'm terribly sorry, but I seem to have ripped my pants.
別惹我 混蛋
Don't try me, punk.
識相的話
Now, wise guy...
就給我快跑去庫房
you run, don't trot...
領條新的
to the supply room, and you get a new pair.
是 長官 我會晚點回來
Yes, sir. I'll be back later in the day.
5分鐘之內回來
Be back in five minutes!
是 長官 見鬼 我聾掉了
Yes, sir. Shit, I'm deaf.
你有棕色的鞋油嗎?
Hey, you got any brown shoe- polish?
有 誰要的?
I've got cordovan. Who's it for?
哈里少尉
Lieutenant Harris.
長官 看 新褲子
Sir! Look, sir, new pants.
你在幹什麼? 把擴音器給我
What are you doing-- ? Give me that.
你們這群豬玀 給你們30分鐘洗澡 然後上課
All right, you scumbags, you have 30 minutes to shower and get to class.
快點 快點
Let's go. Move it. Move it. Move it.
加油 加油
Pick it up. Pick it up.
快點 混蛋
Pick it up, assholes.
到目前為止還沒有人退出
So far, nobody's quit.
不過那是遲早的事
But they will.
好吧
Well, well, well.
我警告過你 不要惹我 小子
I told you not to try me, boy.
站起來
Stand up.
你們兩位班長
Now, I want you two squad leaders...
趕著他跑 直到他倒下
to take Mr. Mahoney here and run him until he throws up.
- 是 - 是
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
等他不行的時候
And then, just after he throws up...
再繼續跑一陣子
run him some more.
- 是 - 是
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
你會知道
You are going to learn, Mahoney...
沒有人．
that nobody...
絕對沒有人．
nobody...
敢於和我．
screws...
過不去
with me.
- 把它撿起來 快 快 - 太棒了
- Pick it up, pick it up! Come on! - Hey, this is great.
- 你們兩個混蛋 快來啊 - 快走
- Two assholes, no waiting. - Move it!
你可不可以讓我來趕他?
Chad, would you please just let me yell at him without interrupting?
- 可以 - 快點 快點
- Sure. - Come on, Mahoney! Move it, move it!
砰
Bang!
這把槍 你是從哪兒弄來的 小子?
Son, where did you get this gun?
- 我媽給的 - 嗯
- My mom gave it to me. - Ah.
哦 我能借用一下嗎?
Can I borrow it for a little while?
當然
Sure.
左 左右左 左 左 左右左
Left, left right left. Left, left, left right left.
你們要學會 赤手空拳的自衛術
You will learn to defend yourselves without stick or firearm.
誰願意上來試一下?
I need a volunteer.
- 巴巴拉 你上來 - 我剛吃飽
- Barbara, get out here. - I just ate.
馬上給我上來 馬上
Right where I'm standing. Right here. Right now.
假設你拿著刀 向我撲過來
All right, come at me with an imaginary knife.
定要這樣做嗎?
Do I have to?
沒錯 我不和你開玩笑
Yes, you do. I'm not joking.
快點 來吧 來吧
Come on. Come on.
- 快 - 嗯
- Now! - Aah!
哎喲
Ouch! Ouch!
就是這麼簡單 誰要做下一個?
Okay. That's how it's done. Who's next?
- 選我 - 我來
- Pick me! - I'd love it. I'd love to go.
我也想來 我們一起
I'd love to go. We'll both go.
你們有二十分鐘
You have 2O minutes to complete the test.
盡可能多答題
Try to answer as many questions as possible.
好的 開始
All right, start.
好了 開始吧 兩次機會 這就是場地
All right, here we go. The count's at two. Here's the pitch.
上 但是失手
Swung on and missed!
出局
Struck out.
嗯 這是星期六的晚上 我感覺很好
Well, it was Saturday night And I was feeling all right
找找我的buttercup
Looking for my buttercup
他們在十三樓的隔壁跳舞
They were dancing next door On the thirteenth floor
你知道嗎 馬洪尼?
You know, Mahoney...
我可以用一個月來修理你
I'd like to spend the next month breaking you into little pieces.
但我不會這麼做
But I won't...
因為你壞透了
because you're bad.
你會影響整個學校的士氣
You're bad for morale, Mahoney.
你看隔壁的小孩
You look like the sweet little boy from next door.
但你騙不了我
Ha. But you don't fool me. Oh, no.
你是個惡魔 骨子裏壞透了
No, you're the devil, and you're rotten to the core.
你破壞了
And you're ruining my chances...
我訓練好警察的機會
of training some men who might make pretty good cops.
我也這麼認為 長官
I agree. I've been saying that.
- 你讓我噁心 - 是的 我讓所有人噁心
- You make me sick. - Thank you, sir. I make everybody sick.
現在 我打個電話給裏德上尉
We're going to pick up this telephone and call your buddy Capt. Reed.
然後 你來告訴他 他送你來這兒 是一個可怕的錯誤
And you. You are going to help me talk him out of this terrible mistake.
太好了 我會盡力的
Terrific. I'll do my part.
你最好這麼做
You're damn right you will.
哈
Ha.
這是警察學校 可否接裏德上尉?
This is the Academy. I'd like to speak to a Capt. Reed.
裏德
Reed!
隊長里德? 嗯 是的 先生 你好嗎 先生?
Captain Reed? Uh, yes, sir. How are you, sir?
這是哈里斯中尉 中尉賽迪斯 哈里斯出在警察學院
This is Lt. Harris, Lt. Thaddeus Harris out at the Police Academy.
真是對不起 打擾您了 先生
I'm so sorry to disturb you, sir...
但你的朋友年輕的馬洪尼想和你談談
but your friend Cadet Mahoney would like to speak with you.
等一下 馬洪尼
Just one moment, please. Mahoney.
- 馬洪尼 - 是
- Mahoney! - Oh, yeah.
你好 裏德上尉 我可以離開這裏嗎?
Hi, Captain Reed? Can I get out of here?
不行? 好的
No? Okay.
我盡力了
I tried.
裏德上尉 非常感謝您
Captain Reed, um, thank you so much.
再見．
Yes. Goodbye. Yes.
我不知道 你想搞什麼鬼
I don't know what you're trying to do.
也不知道 你為什麼來這裏
I don't know why you're here.
但只要我還有一口氣 你就當不了警官
But you'll never be a cop as long as I live.
- 想都不要想 - 從我的桌子上下來 滾出去
- Don't want to be. - Get your butt off my desk.
再警告你一次
And get out of here!
馬洪尼
Mahoney!
我已經告訴過你一次了
I've already told you once.
沒有人 耍得了我
Nobody screws with me.
也許有一天 你碰上了個 合適的姑娘 就會改變的
Well, maybe you'll meet the right girl and all that'll change.
馬上滾出去
Get out of here now!
快點做 馬洪尼 哈里中尉說你得做100個
Come on, Mahoney. Harris said you had to do a hundred.
馬洪尼
Hey, Mahoney.
這是我的臭襪子 我穿了一整天
Here's a pair of my old sweat socks. I wore them all day.
它們會幫你加油的
That should help you to get up.
幹得好
You did it.
你這個狗雜種
You son of a bitch.
他媽的 晚上真無聊
This is a hell of a way to spend my evenings.
我的手 已經沒知覺了
I can't feel my arms anymore.
嘿 巴巴拉 過來
Hey, Barbara, come here.
- 我 - 過來 快來
- Me? - Yeah, come here.
- 怎麼了? - 來 狠狠地打我一下
- What? - Come on, right here.
- 我需要你狠狠地打我一下 - 幹嘛?
- I want you to give me your best shot. - What?
讓你打我 狠狠的打
I want you to hit me. Best shot.
- 打吧 - 快點
- Hit you? - Yeah, come on.
- 真的 - 打我
- Ha, ha. No, really, I - Hit me.
- 說真的 - 現在就做 來吧
- Really, when I - Do it now. Come on.
- 不行 - 我讓你打的
- I can't. Because when I - Do it. Give me your--
行了嗎?
How was that? Was that okay?
夠了嗎?
Yeah.
是的 非常好
Yeah, that's good.
這個週末 是你們第一次休假外出
This weekend is your first leave from the Academy.
無論你們這班垃圾 去哪裏
When you go, wherever it is you filthbags go...
好好享受 外面精彩的世界
do take note of how nice things are on the outside.
好好考慮一下 是不是還要回來
Do give serious consideration to not coming back.
你們中 已經有4人退出了
Four of you have already quit.
好戲才剛開始呢
And that's just the beginning.
立正
Ten-hut!
解散
Dismissed.
他們會開舞會的 一貫如此
Heard him, dismissed! Let's go.
他們會一起參加聚會 他們總是這樣
They'll get together for a party. They always do.
你們也去
You go with them.
如果有什麼出軌行為 立刻給我電話
Whenever they get out of line, give me a ring.
嗨 萊斯利
Hi, Leslie.
這麼用功?
Studying hard?
是啊
Yup.
舞會在哪開?
Where's the party going to be this weekend?
舞會?
Party?
我不知道 有什麼舞會
Party? I don't know anything about a party.
這個週末 我要回家看父母
I'm going home for the weekend and visit my mom and dad.
如果你不介意的話 我要學習了
Now, if you don't mind, I do have to study.
查德 我想他沒有在聽 我們說話
You know, Chad? I don't think we've got his full attention.
我們何不 把他的書丟出窗外?
So why don't you take his books and throw them out the window?
樂意之至 凱爾
My pleasure, Kyle.
查出舞會的地點
Find out where the party is.
- 怎樣查? - 去問馬洪尼
- How? - Ask Mahoney.
- 馬洪尼 - 馬洪尼
- Mahoney. - Mahoney.
1011 1012 1013
Thousand eleven, 1012, 1013...
馬洪尼
Mahoney.
馬洪尼 能借步說話嗎?
Could I speak to you outside for just a second?
好
Yeah.
- 怎麼了- 嗯
- What's up? - Um...
嗯 馬洪尼 額
Uh, Mahoney. Uh...
週末有舞會嗎?
ls there a party this weekend?
當然有啊 你要參加嗎?
Yeah, of course there is. Do you want to come?
不 我來不了
No. No, I can't. Uh...
我只是想知道 在哪裏舉行舞會
I just need to know where it is. Sorry to be asking.
你為什麼問呢?
Then why are you asking?
有人想知道
Some people want to know.
沒問題 這沒什麼大不了 地點在 藍蠔酒吧
Okay, yeah. It's no big secret. It's at the, uh, Blue Oyster bar.
它在豪威爾
It's on Howell.
你為什麼來警校 大個子?
Hey, big boy Why don't you come up
因為我 厭倦了原來的工作
And see me sometime?
嘿 大個子
Hey, big boy
海托華 你呢? 你來學院做什麼?
So, what about you, Hightower? What are you doing at the Academy?
我厭倦了我的職業
I got bored with my chosen profession.
- 那是什麼? - 我曾經是個花農
- What was that? - I was a florist.
園丁?
A florist?
種種花 施施肥
You know, flowers and shit.
是的
Oh, yeah.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 我還以為你不來呢 - 我當然不會錯過
- I didn't think you'd show up. - I wouldn't miss it for the world.
- 想去散散步嗎? - 嗯
- Do you want to go for a walk? - Hmm?
- 散步 - 當然
- Walk. - Oh, yeah.
好啊 你不是開玩笑吧?
Are you kidding? Of course.
- 能說點真心話嗎? - 當然可以
- Can you tell me something? - Yeah?
你為什麼想當警察?
Why do you want to be a cop?
我喜歡打扮得像個男人
I like to dress like a man.
我也是
Me too.
* 今晚你完全屬於我 *
* Tonight you're mine completely *
* 你給我的愛如此甜蜜 *
* You give your love so sweetly *
* 今晚 你眼中閃耀著愛 *
* Tonight the light of love is in your eyes *
* 但是 明天你是否還會愛我 *
* But will you love me tomorrow? *
* 珍貴的愛情是長久的嗎 *
* Is this a lasting treasure *
* 還是片刻的歡愉呢 *
* Or just a moment's pleasure? *
好了 出發 快點快點
Okay, let's go. Move it. Move it. Let's go.
在這裏站兩排
Two lines, right here.
這是第一排 還有第二排
The first one on the step, the second one off.
我說兩排 廢物 走
I said two lines, dummy! Now step it up, step it up, let's go.
喂
Hey.
你們怎麼沒給我電話?
Why didn't you call me this weekend?
沒發生什麼事 長官
Well, uh, nothing really happened, sir.
不是有舞會嗎?
There was a party, wasn't there?
是的 有舞會
Yes, sir.
那麼到底發生了什麼事?
Well, what went on?
只是跳舞 長官
Dancing, sir.
純跳舞
Mostly dancing.
跳舞?
Dancing?
高個子 你先來 快
Hightower, you're first. Let's go.
跟我來
Come with me.
嗯
Uh...
我準備好了 長官
Ready now, sir.
謝謝
Uh, thank you.
我打中了
I got him.
泰格貝利 你來
Tackleberry. You're next.
跟我來
Come with me.
- 嘿 - 泰格貝利
- Hey! - Tackleberry!
見鬼了
Holy shit.
給我回來
Get back here.
- 是的 警官 - 是"女警官"
- Yes, sir. - Yes, ma'am.
- 別急 我可以解釋的 - 閉嘴
- Don't worry, I can explain everything. - Shut up.
- 是的 先生 - 應該叫"女警官"
- Yes, sir. - Yes, ma'am.
是的 女警官
Yes, ma'am.
幾個星期以來 你每天晚上都潛進這裏偷情
You've been sneaking in here every night for weeks.
什麼? 不是那樣的
What? No.
你說我該如何懲罰你呢?
What do you think I ought to do about this?
讓我想想
Well, let's see. Uh...
天吶
My God.
警官?
Sir.
叫"女警官"
Ma'am.
一位警官 必須縣備尊嚴及信心
A police officer must generate respect and confidence.
聲音與尊嚴 信心
His or her voice, Hooks...
有密切的關係 胡克絲 出來
has a great deal to do with that. Hooks, get up. Stand right over here.
胡克絲 出來
Today, Hooks.
這是間房子
Now, here is the house.
這是窗戶
Here is the window.
而我是個賊
And I am a burglar.
我從窗子爬出來
I am coming out of the window...
手裏拿著了一部音響
with a stolen stereo in my hand.
我爬出窗戶 越過籬笆
I'm coming out of the window, over the hedge...
而你是位警官
and you are the arresting officer.
你會怎麼說? 胡克絲?
What do you say, Hooks?
別動 這是搶劫
Don't move! This is a stickup.
搶劫?
Stickup?
我是說 我是警察 住手
I mean, police-- Police officer. Stop.
坐下吧 胡克絲
Sit down, Hooks.
去 去 去 你真沒用
Sit, sit, sit.
泰格貝利 你來示範 同樣的 情景
Tackleberry, you try it. Same situation.
這是間房子 這是窗戶
All right. Here is the house. Here is the window.
我是個賊 正從屋子裏爬出來
I'm the burglar. I'm coming out of the house, over the hedge...
手裏捧著偷來的音響
I've got the stolen stereo in my hands.
在我轟掉你的腦袋之前 快放下那音響 混蛋
Drop that stereo before I blow your goddamn nuts off, asshole!
泰格貝利 我們真要好好談談
Tackleberry, we really need to talk.
馬洪尼 我想問你個問題
Mahoney, let me ask you a question.
嗯
Hmm?
你是否曾經碰到一個
Have you ever had a woman just...
飢餓如狼的女人?
throw you down and screw your goddamn brains out?
沒有吧
Uh, no.
昨晚我碰到了
It happened to me last night.
真的 結果怎樣?
Really? How was it?
我想
I think, uh...
我戀愛了
I'm in love.
哇哦
Wow.
- 有多少個姑娘 - 只有一個
- How many girls were there? - Just one.
就一個?
Just one?
你只和一個女孩做愛?
You made love to just one girl?
不會吧
That's disgusting.
我知道很反常
Yeah, I know.
- 別怪我多嘴 - 嗯
- Hey, George, can I ask you something? - Sure.
有的時候
Every now and then, uh...
有時候 你的西班牙語口音 好像消失了
you seem to lose your Spanish accent.
怎麼回事?
What's up?
只是有時候
Yeah. Every now and then.
你可以保密嗎?
Can you keep a secret?
可以
Oh, yeah.
我並不是喬治．馬丁
I'm not really George Martin.
我只是一個普通的美國人
I'm just plain old George Martin, fourth-generation American. Ha, ha.
- 真的嗎? - 我只是用這口音來把馬子
- Really? - I just use the accent to get the girls.
- 有用嗎? - 當然有用
- Does it work? - Eh.
- 芭芭拉 - 他在體育館
- Barbara! - Uh, he's in the gym.
你會為欺騙我們 而付出代價的
You're gonna pay for sending us to the wrong party.
- 我要告訴他 - 我們不會只罰你做伏臥撐的
- I'll tell him. - Not just pushups, either, Leslie.
我們要把你扔出去
We're gonna get your fat ass thrown out of here. That's a promise!
- 那又怎樣? - 怎樣?
- How? - How?
你會知道的
You'll find out.
不只馬洪尼 會耍花樣
Mahoney isn't the only one here who can play tricks.
慢點 這又不是跑鞋
Hey, hey. Take it easy. These ain't track shoes.
快點
Yeah, I know. Just hurry up.
我已經很快了 這裏讓我覺得不舒服
I'm as anxious as you. I'm not comfortable in these surroundings.
- 快上來 - 在上面?
- Yeah, well, come on up. - Up here?
- 好吧 - 我什麼時候 可以拿到餘下的錢?
- Yeah, yeah. - Hey, listen, when do I get my money?
事成之後
When the job's over, for crying out loud.
很好 你可以去那邊 坐下休息一下
That's good, Hightower. Why don't you just sit down over there?
你們這群人渣 30分鐘後檢查房間
All right, you scumballs, 30 minutes to room inspection.
快
Move it. Move it. Move it.
- 嘿 親愛的 - 嘿
- Hi, honey. - Hi. Uh...
- 有火嗎? - 嗯
- Got a light? - Uh...
我不吸煙 不過 我有個吸煙的朋友 我去找他
I don't smoke. Ha, ha. I have a friend who smokes. I'll go get him.
馬洪尼 大麻煩
Mahoney, major problem.
好吧 我的天啊
Well, my goodness.
你能不能冷靜一點 放輕鬆點?
Would you please just calm down and take it easy?
我只是想 在另一個地方做愛 就是這樣
I just like to do it in strange places, that's all. Okay?
你怎麼不早說?
Why the hell didn't you say so?
這所學校 是全國最完善的學府
You'll find this academy one of the most comprehensive in the country.
並且有許多特色
I could point out many, many, many features to you. Um...
- 擠進去? - 在這裏面
- Squeeze in here. Yeah. - In here?
- 你想在講台下面幹嗎? - 求之不得
- You want to do it in a podium? - All my life.
- 你去哪兒? - 我要回去
- Right. Where you going? - I'll be back.
我不是你的官人 他待會就到
I'm not the customer. The real customer will be here any second now, okay?
好的
Oh, okay.
各位 請隨我來
Gentlemen, please follow me.
我們準備了很精彩的
We have a very, very fine...
幻燈片要呈現給各位
slide presentation for you.
請坐
Please take your seats.
這裏有足夠的座位
I think you'll find there's plenty of room for everybody.
謝謝
Thank you.
首先我很遺憾
First of all, I'd like to say how sorry I am...
大家沒有到齊
that everybody could not make it today.
我相信 在座的各位 將會發現這個幻燈片非常有趣—
For those here, I think you'll find the presentation interesting...
非常激動人心
as well as very, very stimulating.
請將燈光調暗
Could we have the lights turned down?
這是第一張幻燈——片
Now, this first slide...
非常非常
shows a very...
有趣的是
very interesting thing:
這是我們的主樓
Our main building.
這第二
In slide two...
張幻燈片
We see...
是主樓的另一個
another view...
角度
of it.
哦 上帝啊 真是難以置信
Oh, my God. You wouldn't believe it.
請讓我們靜靜地欣賞這副幻燈片
Let us look at this slide for a moment, without comment.
一圖抵千字
I think it speaks for itself.
請開燈
Could we have the lights, please?
好了
Well.
我希望 你們和我一樣 喜歡這場幻燈片
I hope this was as much fun for you as it was for me.
現在 讓我們共進午餐吧
Let's have lunch, shall we?
或許 再來根煙
And maybe, smoke a cigarette.
講得真好
Good speech.
你打算怎麼對付馬洪尼?
What do you intend to do about Mahoney?
- 他幹了些什麼? - 他幹了些什麼?
- What's he done? - What's he done?
我來告訴你 他幹了些什麼?
I'll tell you what he's done. He...
是
Yes, sir?
他幹了一件很壞的事
He did a very, very bad thing.
對誰幹的 長官?
To whom, sir?
對誰?
To whom?
額
Yes, sir.
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
您還好嗎 長官?
Are you all right, sir?
不好 我可以走了嗎?
No, not really. May I go?
- 當然可以 - 謝謝
- Of course, sir. - Thank you.
不用謝
You're welcome.
左 右 左 左 左
Left, right, left. Left. Left.
左 右 左 左
Left, right, left. Left.
左 右 左 左 左 左 右 左
Left, right, left. Left. Left. Left, right, left.
從現在開始 你們將會駕駛
From now on, part of your training will be to ride, from time to time...
真正的警車 由正式警官陪同
in actual squad cars with actual police officers...
進行實景訓練
in actual situations.
你們最好 少說廢話
And you'd better actually keep your mouths shut.
睜大眼睛 豎起耳朵
And your eyes and your ears open.
馬洪尼 你和我同行
Say, Mahoney, why don't you ride with me?
好了 出發 快點 快點
Well, move it, cretins! Move it, move it, move it!
哈里少尉 我突然改變主意了 我想當個好警察
Lieutenant Harris, I've changed my mind. I want to be a cop.
- 別想 臭小子 - 為什麼不行? 我只要乖乖的
- Never, punk. - Why not? All I have to do is behave--
下車 聽見沒有?
Get out of this car, Mahoney. You hear me?
快滾出去 跟在我後面 混小子
You get. Get, Mahoney. You get out there and you follow me.
跟在我後面 混小子
You stay right behind me, punk.
我真喜歡 在鄉野間兜風
Oh, how I love a ride in the country.
警官 警官
Officer. Officer.
請你幫我 把樹上的貓咪弄下來 好嗎?
Can you get my kitty-cat out of the tree?
沒問題 夫人
No problem, ma'am.
哦 不 等等
Oh, no. No, wait.
搞什麼鬼?
What the hell is this?
我馬上回來
I'll be right back. I'm sorry.
那邊是怎麼回事?
What the hell is going on down there?
快走
Move it!
混蛋
Assholes.
嘿 你 把摩托車給我
Hey! Hey, you, give me that bike.
我們是警察 走開
Come on, move it. This is official police business. Move it out. Let's go.
- 它還是新的 - 放心 我不會弄壞它的
- It's new. - Don't worry, I'm not gonna hurt it.
唉
Whoa!
哦 上帝啊
My God.
快去叫獸醫來
Someone call a veterinarian.
長官 您的新帽子
Your new hat, sir.
你沒告訴任何人吧l
You told no one?
絕對沒有
Not a soul.
高個子?
Hightower? Hightower?
我想找你幫忙
I need to talk.
我很樂意 高個子 不過
That's terrific, Hightower, but it's, uh...
現在是凌晨2:30
It's 2:30 in the morning.
- 明天駕駛測驗 - 然後呢?
- The driving course is tomorrow. - So?
我從十二歲開始 就沒碰過車子
I haven't driven a car since I was 12.
你在開玩笑?
Really? You're kidding.
哈里說 如果不能通過 我就得滾蛋
If I don't pass this driving course, they're gonna kick me out. Harris said so.
好吧 我們走
All right. Let's go.
也沒什麼好睡的
Sleeping is for fags.
首先 我們得弄輛車來 科普蘭的車應該行
First thing we gotta do is steal a car. Copeland's should do.
好了 輪到你了
Okay, your turn.
你要記住 駕駛得穩一點
Now, you've got to remember to drive defensively...
還是冒險一點
or offensively, depending on your needs. Let's go.
舒服嗎?
Comfy?
- 不 - 好吧
- No. - All right.
好 我們把座位挪後一點
Let's just move the seat back a little.
乾脆把前座拆掉
On second thought, let's rip the front seats out and sit in the back.
其實 我是說著玩的 不過這樣也好
I was kidding about the front seat. But this is good.
坐得舒服最重要
It's different. Comfort's important.
進一檔 對 再踩踩油門 現在可以開得快一點了
Put it into first. Right. Little more. Okay, you can go a little faster now.
對 對 你開的很好
Yeah. Yeah, you're doing beautifully. You feel it? You feel what's going on?
你可以關掉雨刷
You can even turn off the windshield wipers.
是的
Yeah, that's it.
好 前面有車子
Okay, now there's another car.
海托華
Hightower?
海托華 你幹麼不踩剎車?
Hightow-- ? What-- ? You didn't hit the brakes.
你沒叫我踩
You didn't tell me to.
白癡
You idiot!
你這個混蛋 看你幹的好事
You bastard! You dumb shit!
- 先停在一邊 讓我開吧 - 不 現在不行
- Pull over and let me drive for a while. - No, not now.
真好玩
This is fun.
- 停下來吧 - 不 看我怎麼甩掉他們
- Pull over. - No, I'm getting out of here.
好樣的 大個
Holy shit!
是我教他的
Attaboy, Hightower.
幹得不賴
Taught him everything he knows.
不賴
Not bad.
胡克絲 到你了
Miss Hooks, you're next.
快
Hurry up!
謝了 馬洪尼 你救了我一命
Thanks, Mahoney. You saved my life.
- 也許有一天 輪到你來救我了 - 任何時候
- Maybe someday you'll save mine. - Any time.
下一個 黃線
You're next. Yellow line. Yellow line.
不要哭
You better not cry
別噘嘴 因為聖誕老人就來了
You better not pout I'm telling you why
一點點
Wee!
真有趣
Oh, this is fun.
嗷 嗷 嗷
Ow! Ow! Ow!
怎麼回事?
What is it? What is it?
她軋到了我的腳
She ran over my feet.
我真的很抱歉
I'm sorry. I really am.
對不起? 你這塊愚蠢的黑炭
Sorry? You dumb, fat jigaboo!
哦 該死
Oh, shit.
- 你冷靜點 大個子 - 沒事了
- At ease, Hightower. At ease. - It's okay, Hightower.
- 他不是有意的 只是在說笑 - 放鬆點
- He didn't mean it. He was joking. - Take it easy, now. Hightower!
停手
Hightower, don't do that.
你不住手的話 馬上就滾蛋 我警告你 大個子1
If you don't stop, you are out of here. I am warning you, Hightower!
你闖下大禍了
You messed up big, mister.
你 馬上捲鋪蓋 立刻給我滾
Now you get your stuff and get out of here, right now.
拿著
Get!
請注意 摩托維修的申請表
Attention, applications for motorcycle service...
必須在週五之前上交
should be turned in at the Administration building by Friday.
申請摩托車服務應打開
Applications for motorcycle service should be turned in...
走了一個 其他的人也會走的
One down, several to go.
科普蘭 快從車子裏出來
Copeland, get out of that car.
是馬洪尼干的
Mahoney.
定是馬洪尼干的 我明白的
It's got to be Mahoney.
我知道
I know, I know. Come on.
在我們當中 大個肯定能成為警官的
Out of all the people I thought would make it, Hightower was the one.
如果所有的警察 都像大個那樣 這世界上就沒有罪惡了
I mean, if all the cops looked like him, there'd be no crime at all.
我要離開這鬼地方
I'm getting sick of this place.
還好嗎? 馬洪尼?
How're you doing, "Ma-homo"?
現在可別惹我 布朗克
Don't fool with me. Not in the mood.
你弄壞了我的車
You wrecked my car.
不 是大個干的 去找他吧 如果你打得過他的話
No, Hightower did. Why don't you go see him? That'd be a matchup.
不過 我們就要找你
Because we want you.
那麼 就在午夜12點 來沙灘找我
Okay, how about, uh, 12:00 midnight? Nine o'clock on the coast.
我就要現在 讓你先動手
No, no. I'm talking right now, Mahoney. Let's go. You throw the first punch.
打架是會被開除的
Cadet could get thrown out...
- 打另一位學員 - 真的嗎?
- for hitting another cadet. - Oh, really?
我以為你想被開除呢
I thought you wanted to get thrown out.
現在機會來了
Here's your chance.
不
No.
馬洪尼 我要把這個抹在你的臉上
Now, Mahoney, I'm going to rub this right in your face.
各就各位
On your mark...
接招
get set--
- 等等 你們這些傢伙 等等 - 你們在幹什麼?
- Wait, you guys! Wait! - What the hell-- ?
是誰先打起來的?
Who threw the first punch?
- 我只想知道這個 - 是巴巴拉先動手的
- That's all I want to know. - Barbara did.
- 巴巴拉? - 是的
- Barbara? - That's right, sir.
那麼他還有他的怪狗可以滾蛋了
Then he's out of here. Him and his queer dog.
等等 不是巴巴拉先動手的
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Barbara didn't throw the first punch.
- 他那樣做 - 我就打了他
- He did so. - I threw the punch.
馬洪尼 你瘋了嗎?
Mahoney, you're out of your mind. Lieutenant--
- 布朗克 你說吧 - 布朗克 真的嗎?
- Blankes, who'd you rather have out? - Is that true, Blankes?
是馬洪尼先動手的嗎?
Did Mahoney start it?
是 長官 是他先動手的
Yes, sir. Mahoney started it.
馬洪尼 我的小壞蛋
Then, Mahoney, my little piss-ant...
你被開除了 永遠
you are out of the Academy...
forever.
快收拾你的行李
Get your stuff.
滾蛋
And get out.
真是不幸 拜拜
Too bad, so sad, bye-bye.
收音機妨礙到你們了嗎?
Does the radio bother you?
我可以把音量關小的
I could turn it down.
我給你拿了個蘋果
Here, I brought you an apple.
謝謝
Thanks.
嗨
Hey, man, what-- ?
唉
Whoa!
老天 拿著
My God. Here, take this.
嘿 免費的電視機
Hey, free TV's.
大家聽著 外面有暴亂
Hey, everybody! There's a riot going on.
我的生活 你毀了我
My livelihood! You're ruining me!
你得到了什麼? 你這是幹什麼用的電視?
What do you got there? What are you doing with that TV?
- 嘿 要搭車嗎? - 不 謝謝
- Hi. Want a ride? - No, thanks.
你們倆 聽到電台播出的新聞了嗎?
Hey, did you two hear the news...
沒有
- on the radio? - No.
- 市中心發生了大暴亂 - 怎麼可能
- A riot's broken out downtown. - How come?
誰也不知道 是怎麼回事
Who knows how these things get started?
所有的警校生
Attention! All cadets report immediately...
即刻穿上防暴裝備
to the parking lot in full riot gear.
到停車場集合
Repeat, all cadets report immediately to the parking lot in full riot gear.
這不是演習
This is not a drill.
- 喬斯 是你搞的鬼嗎? - 不 沒有
- Jones! Was that you? - No, man.
快走 快走
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
快點 快點
Get out there fast! Move it, move it, move it!
快走 快走
Let's go, let's go.
機會來了
This is it. This is the big one.
該我
It's time this cop...
大顯身手了
met the public.
各位注意聽著 情況如下
All right, listen up. Here's the situation. There is a state...
市區發生了大暴亂
of general disorder in the Oakfield section of town.
警察正在努力控制局面
Real police are handling the problem.
我們被派往外圍的安全地區
We are being sent to a peripheral safe area.
我們的任務是疏散交通
Our job will be merely to divert traffic away from the trouble zone...
及保護公共財產安全
and to protect public property.
你們將會使用實彈
You will have live ammunition...
但是沒有命令 讓你們開火
but there will be no call to use it.
尤其是你 泰格貝利 你明白嗎?
Tackleberry, do you understand, numb nuts?
明白
Yes, sir.
走吧
Come on!
我們現在 進入百爾幕地區的高速公路
We are now entering the expressway at Belmont.
非常好 你們的任務區域是在第十六街
Very good. Your bus is to deploy on Sixteenth Street...
在第4區和第8區之間
between 4th and 8th Avenues.
十六街 你確定嗎? 長官?
Sixteenth Street? Are you sure, sir?
當然確定
Of course I'm sure. I never forget a number.
是
Yes, sir.
這裏一個人都沒有
There's nobody around.
我想他們是藏起來了
I guess they're hiding.
好吧 我們走吧 讓我們繼續前進吧
All right, let's go, dirtbags, unload it. Let's move it.
我需要這裏有兩行人 來吧 假人
I want two lines right here. Come on, dummies.
走吧 走吧
Let's go, let's go.
好 走吧 走吧 快
You, one block over, one block up.
你 後面 你 下面
You, one block down.
你 後面
You, one block up. You, one block over.
快 快
You, one block over. Let's go. Let's go.
逮捕中…
If you have to make an arrest...
要盡量保待安靜
do it as quietly as possible.
這裏很平靜
Boy, it sure is quiet around here, huh?
情況如何呀 費克勒
Hey, Fackler. How's it going?
很好 謝謝
Oh, just fine, thanks.
- 你在這裏弄什麼鬼呀? - 我們是警校的
- What the hell are you doing here? - We're from the Academy.
你們不是應該在外圍嗎? 暴亂就在這條街
You're supposed to be blocks away. The damn riot's right down this street.
我們正在撤出
We're pulling out.
我愛吃壽司 喜歡日本貸
I love sushi. I'm into back-rubs, all kinds of Japanese stuff.
我的汽車音響就是索尼的
My car stereo, it's a Sony.
我有個朋友的父親 就死在珍珠港
I got a good friend, his father was killed at Pearl Harbor.
也許跟你的家庭有些關聯
Hey, maybe your family had something to do with it?
你知道日本清酒嗎?
You know sake? The wine?
我知道他們在哪兒加工
I know a place where they heat it up before they serve it.
見鬼
Holy shit.
我要溜了
I got to go now.
快跑
Run!
嘿 我來檢閱了
Hello, men. I thought I'd come by for a personal inspection.
- 我們可以上車嗎 長官? - 當然可以
- Okay if we get in, sir? - I guess so.
為什麼不呢? 情況如何?
Sure, why not? Well, men, how's it going?
給我詳細報告
I want you to give me a fix on the entire situation.
情況似乎很糟 長官
Not that good, sir.
真的太糟了
Oh, so this is very, very, very bad.
首先 不要慌
The main thing is not to panic.
注意 各位請注意
Attention! Attention, everybody.
我是警官學校的馬薩校長
Attention. This is Commandant Eric Lassard of the Police Academy.
如果你們不疏散 我就會拘捕你們
If you do not disperse immediately, my men will have to arrest you.
給你們五秒的時間 離開現場
You have five seconds to move away. Five. Four. Three. Two. One.
把那個給我
Give me the thing.
你應該去做泊車仔 長官
You should park cars for a living, sir.
你們誰想嘗嘗子彈?
Anybody want any of this?
嘿 說你呢 想找死嗎?
You want this? You'd die for this.
- 現在怎麼不神氣啦? - 來吧
- You're not so tough now. - Come and take it.
- 你怎麼樣? 你要這個? - 怎麼了?
- How about you? You want this? - What's the matter?
- 我在跟你說話呢 白癡 - 想找死嗎?
- I'm talking to you, twerp. - Just too dumb to talk, huh?
該死 進去吧
Damn it. Look, in here.
試試這邊
Try this one.
萊斯利·巴巴拉 請求支援
Help. Help. This is Cadet Leslie Barbara. Help.
巴巴拉 我是哈里少尉
Barbara, this is Lt. Harris.
先冷靜下來
Just calm down.
我後面有30多個暴民
I'm being chased by 30 rioters.
巴巴拉 告訴我你的位置
Barbara, just tell me where you are.
我看見你了 長官
I'm passing you now, sir.
老天
Holy shit.
你好嗎?
Hi.
去抓警察
Get the cops!
嗯
Uh...
站在原處別動
Okay. Hold it right there, guys.
嘿 這不是巴巴拉警官嗎
Why, if it isn't Leslie Barbara...
- 警察 - 是的
- the police officer. - Yeah.
萊斯利 你不會向我們開槍的
Come on, Les, you're not going to shoot us.
你不會殺老朋友 對吧
You wouldn't shoot old friends, would you?
不
No.
萊斯利
Les.
趕快消失 我們正忙
Get lost. We're busy.
現在 把家俱搬回去 趕快滾
Now, get the furniture back up there and get out of the area.
家俱是我們的呀
But it's our furniture.
哦
Oh.
抱歉
Sorry.
卡拉漢呼叫哈里
Callahan calling Harris. Come in, please.
快回答
Harris, come in.
哈里死到哪兒去了?
Where the hell is Harris?
- 我不知道 - 什麼?
- I don't know. - What?
- 她不知道 - 我聽見了
- She doesn't know. - I heard her.
快跑
Run!
為什麼不還擊?
Why don't you shoot back?
- 是槍聲 - 真槍
- Are those gunshots? - Fucking A.
還擊啊 趕快
Shoot back. Come on.
看那上面
Look up there. See? See?
好像是哈利中尉在上面
That looks like Harris up there.
我們要還擊嗎?
Should we shoot back?
嗯
Hmm.
不行了吧
I don't think so.
還擊啊
Come on!
待在那兒 別動
Stay there.
馬洪尼
Mahoney!
哦 該死 這該死的
Oh, shit. Oh, shit, oh, shit, oh, shit.
我想 應該有後門可以上去
I'll bet there's a back door to this place.
胡克絲 回來
Hooks. Hooks! Hooks, get the hell back here.
這是命令
That's an order.
別動
Freeze!
哦 該死
Oh, shit.
別動 混蛋
Don't move, you bastard.
快跑 湯普森
Run, Thompson! Run!
把槍放下
Put the gun down.
應該是你把槍放下
Let's say you put your gun down.
有什麼好主意嗎 長官?
Lieutenant Harris, any last-minute tips or suggestions?
我腦子裏一片空白
Nothing really comes to mind.
你打算怎麼辦?
What's it gonna be?
把槍扔遠點
Throw your gun over the ledge.
現在我有兩隻人質了
I got two piglet-wigglets.
嘿
Hey!
你想怎樣?
What do you want?
我要看著他們死
I want to watch you off these pigs.
當然
Sure. Ha, ha. Sure.
- 先殺哪一個? - 額
- Which one do we do first? - Hmm.
先殺這個吧
I believe I'd shoot this one.
好 就先幹掉老傢伙
Yeah, the old one.
- 看起來像是學生用的左輪手槍 - 原來是他們兩個混球
- Looks like cadet revolvers to me. - I know those guys.
別動 混蛋
Don't move, dirtbag!
嘿
Hey. Aw. Hey, hey.
- 嘿 - 他怎麼了?
- Hey, hey, hey. - What's wrong with this man?
他錯過了一場槍戰 長官
There was gunplay, sir, and he missed it.
- 哈里斯中尉? 裏德上尉 - 很高興見到你 長官
- Lieutenant Harris? Captain Reed. - Nice to meet you, sir.
謝謝你 幫我照顧馬洪尼
Thank you. I also want to thank you for looking out for Mahoney.
願意效勞 長官
It was an honor and a pleasure, sir.
謝謝
Thank you, sir. Ha, ha.
- 你怎麼了? - 這女人 給你惹麻煩嗎?
- Could you just-- ? - This woman bothering you?
這是我母親
What? Uh, no. This is my mother.
很好 繼續
Ten-four. Carry on.
- 哦 我的寶貝 - 媽媽 會
- Oh, my precious - Mom, would-- ?
- 8點鐘 你要見見我的母親 - 好的
- Then at 8:00 you'll meet my mother. - Right.
- 你最好帶束花去 - 是的 記得帶花
- You'd better have some flowers. - Flowers, check.
你們快停下
You men, stop that.
哦
Oh, well, ha, ha.
這才像話 馬洪尼
That's more like it, Mahoney.
繼續吧
Good man. Keep up the good work.
謝謝
Thank you, sir.
各位先生 各位女士 歡迎警官學校的拉薩校長
Ladies and gentlemen, the commandant of the Academy, Eric Lassard.
本屆的警校畢業生 創造了許多 不凡的事跡
So many unusual events have happened to this graduating class...
我很激動
and to me, also.
我可以告訴各位 許多許多的故事
I could tell you many, many stories, but instead...
但我想 先說兩句
I have a presentation to make.
在過去 從未有學生獲得過
No Academy cadet has ever received the highest award...
警務部頒發的最高榮譽
this police department has to make.
但今天 卻有兩位同學 要接受頒獎
Today, there are two:
莫斯警官
Officers Moses Hightower...
馬洪尼警官
and Carey Mahoney.
請上台來
Gentlemen, please step forward.
說幾句話吧
You are both expected to make a few short remarks.
有請莫斯警官
Officer Hightower.
謝謝
Thanks.
非常… 非常… 好
That was very, very, very good.
有請馬洪尼警官
Officer Mahoney.
謝謝拉薩校長 警長
Thank you, Commandant Lassard, Chief Hurnst...
市長夫人 總統先生
Madam Mayor, Mr. President...
挪威國王
His Holiness the Pope, the King of Norway...
以及各位貴賓
and our other honored guests.